[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 07]
It's almost a month away.
I wonder if Lu Li has figured it out yet.
Senior Bai Feng.
Why are you here?
Why can't I be here?
I'm closer to Lu Li
than you think.
He's resting.
I don't think it's a good time for you
to go in there.
Liu Shao.
Everyone in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion knows that
you are in conflict with his spiritual power.
You were born to be
the malefic of his life.
Think about it.
You
only knows buy him off.
Once you're no longer useful,
he will not hesitate to leave you behind.
He's
such a cold and greedy man.
Senior.
Although Lu Li always
talks about money,
he wears the cheapest fabric,
and eats the cheapest food when he eats out.
He kept the money he had saved in his pocket
and was reluctant to spend it.
Although I don't know
why he hides
his true self,
my father told me
you can't judge a man
by his appearance. You need to see his heart.
So I trust him.
I don't believe he's the man you say he is.
I can't believe Liu Shao would defend me like that.
Silly girl.
I'm looking out for you here.
If something goes wrong,
don't blame me for not warning you.
I appreciate your efforts.
I still remember the time
when you brought Du Mingchong to the Pearl Pavilion
and put a sword around my neck.
Liu Shao trusts me.
I can't let her down.
I must help her find the King Herb as soon as possible.
Liu Shao.
What happened?
You don't want to find the King Herb?
You've figured it out?
Well, it's not really a solution.
But at this time,
we can only go to the Pearl Pavilion to find him,
to use some
very unusual measures.
[Pearl Pavilion]
Shut up.
You kicked me?
Behave yourself.
Don't move.
Master of Herbs, right?
You let us play with you every day, right?
And you won't tell us
how to grow the King Herb, right?
Right?
Now,
I give you two choices.
Two choices.
First.
Hush.
Give us the King Herb.
King Herb.
Second.
Can you stop talking?
Okay.
Well, second.
Give us the King Herb.
Otherwise...
I'm gonna cook you right now.
Think of a way
to keep you alive
and give us the King Herb.
That's right.
What are you talking about?
What did he say?
I can't hear you.
Louder.
How dare you two little bastards
do this to me?
I'm telling you.
You can't
get spiritual power
from eating the King Herb.
I've lived in the Pearl Pavilion
for thousands of years.
I don't bow down to anyone.
Eat, eat as you please!
Choke you to death!
He's a little arrogant?
And he doesn't bow his head?
Liu Shao.
Come on.
You! You! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Take a guess. Don't move.
Behave yourself.
Give it back to me!
This hairpin looks familiar.
Remember?
This is the one
from the portrait in the "Magic Plant Code".
Right.
The beauty in the painting
wore
this hairpin.
Was she right, master?
I'm telling you.
How dare you two do this to me?
If there's any damage to this hairpin,
I'll keep you from seeing the sun tomorrow.
Is he really angry?
Master,
actually,
we don't want to push you like this, okay?
We couldn't help it.
We're at the end of our tether.
If we can't find the King Herb,
you really want Liu Shao out
to feed the demons?
Yes, I can't beat Ao Hen.
And I can't run away.
You can't just
let this happen.
Actually, there're some things
that you can't do with your best efforts.
For example?
For example,
if you can help me out of the Pearl Pavilion,
I'll give you the King Herb.
What do you think?
That's it?
Deal.
But you have to let us know
how you got in here, right?
It happened
because I was too kind.
A thousand years ago,
I was bored, so I came to the mortal world.
There was nothing interesting.
And I saw her in the moonlight.
She seemed to have something on her mind.
This scene caught my eye at once.
Miss!
Miss. Miss.
Miss, wake up.
Miss.
Wake up.
Why do you want to die?
You want to know?
You can meet me at the Pearl Pavilion
between 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. tomorrow afternoon.
I'll tell you my story.
Pearl Pavilion?
By the way,
my name is Ling Xueyang.
Ling Xueyang?
This girl is so pretty.
And she has a nice name, too.
Looks like heaven really heard my call.
I not only met interesting things,
but also interesting people.
How can you be smiling?
Of course I can.
That was a hero saving the beauty,
beautiful as a fairy tale.
According to legend,
there was
a very outstanding female Marquis Wuyang,
named Ling Xueyang.
Marquis Wuyang
jumped into the river and killed herself?
And she happened to be saved
by you?
So what?
Anyway,
this... this... this was a good start!
Okay, okay, okay.
Have a seat.
A good start.
Did you go on your date?
Did you?
Of course.
But it didn't occur to me that
I wouldn't be able to come back.
Ling Xueyang, I'm coming!
Ling Xueyang.
What do you mean?
By the way,
I,
Ling Xueyang,
[Ling Xueyang, female Marquis Wuyang]
am the current Marquis Wuyang,
the Lord of the human world.
Marquis Wuyang?
So throwing yourself in the lake and killing yourself
were deliberate attempts to get close to me?
What exactly do you want to do?
I want your King Herb.
I don't have.
If not,
you can stay.
I don't care.
Let's see which one of us can outlive the other.
But you can't stew me.
In this way,
I was left by Xueyang in the Pearl Pavilion.
[Pearl Pavilion]
She spent her days at the pavilion reading papers
and dealing with official businesses.
She didn't even look at me.
I was bored
with her every day.
So I couldn't help teasing her.
She ignored me
and was not angry.
Gradually,
I got used to the Pearl Pavilion,
and got used to be with her every day.
Until one night,
I woke up and didn't see her.
For thousands of years of loneliness,
I felt this warmth for the first time.
I didn't know since when
I looked forward to seeing her every second of the day,
accompanying her.
She was still cold
and unsmiling.
But gradually we began to care about each other.
My life
had never been so peaceful
and happy.
Because of her,
I became a real person,
not just a herb.
And then what happened?
She died?
Hey.
Watch your mouth.
Okay, okay, okay.
Our master
just took advantage of his long life.
Was she dead?
How can you talk this way?
Actually,
I'm worried that
mortal life is too short.
I was ready to give her the herb.
Do you know
why I want your herb?
Because I want to draw the Moon Sword.
I want the greatest power in the world.
I want mortals
to live righteously between heaven and earth,
no longer be bullied by demons
and no longer be restrained by immortals.
And we wouldn't be like this.
Without the help of immortals,
I can't even deal with a drought-causing monster.
At that moment,
I wanted to give her the King Herb
to reassure her.
But
I hesitated.
This moment of hesitation
has become our eternal farewell.
Don't open it until I leave.
And then?
What happened?
Legend has it that
Ling Xueyang died with that monster
in the great war.
It snowed for three days.
And the people wept for her for three days.
According to historical records,
heaven pitied her love for the people,
so it snowed for three days for her funeral.
If only I had given her the herb
and helped her draw the Moon Sword.
Master,
don't be sad.
Yes.
I'm sure Ling Xueyang would hate to see you like this.
Let's go.
Let's leave him alone.
Let's not push him.
I didn't expect him to live 10,000 years
and still have a past like this.
Even if he doesn't give us the herb,
let's get him out.
Liu Shao.
Did you ever wonder
why Ling Xueyang gave him that hairpin?
Did Ling Xueyang feel that she couldn't come back,
so she used this to show her heart?
It's possible.
But I don't think that's what she meant.
The hairpin may have something to do with the boundary.
Ling Xueyang knew she was going to die.
How could she
keep her sweetheart imprisoned for thousands of years?
But this hairpin
was supposed to be the only memento
of Ling Xueyang.
Even if we get him out,
it's not gonna help.
What really held him back
was his feelings for Ling Xueyang.
So,
we don't have much chance of getting the herb, do we?
Lu Li.
If I get kicked out,
will you stand with me
to face Ao Hen?
I don't know how far I can go with you.
But I will do my best
to accompany you to go on.
Liu Shao.
I can actually relate to Ling Xueyang now,
drawing the Moon Sword
to get strong power,
so you can protect the people you're trying to protect.
From now on,
I'll stand with you in the face of anyone
and anything.
I hope one day
I can be strong enough to protect you
from anyone and anything.
Lu Li.
Thank you.
Ao Hen!
Come out!
You don't look like a daredevil.
Don't you dare come and yell at me.
I see
you've figured it out.
Ao Hen,
I want to make a deal with you.
Will you?
You?
What qualifications do you have
to make this deal with me?
I'm certainly no match for you
in strength.
But I know you've been chasing someone.
I can help you get Liu Shao.
Okay.
I wonder
what you
really want.
I want to be strong,
like you.
Tell me
how strong I am.
You can ask for anything you want,
without asking anyone
and caring whether he agrees or not.
All right.
I'll grant your request.
Tell me.
What exactly do you want?
Every year, banishing demons on the Double Ninth Festival
is a top priority in the mansion.
The weather is dry these days
and it's easy to catch fire.
Be careful, all of you.
No place in this mansion
can be left behind.
Yes.
Wang Jian.
Come here.
Why isn't Lu Li here again?
What did he do
while we were busy?
Does he have eyes for me?
Senior, calm down.
The Lord and Captain Fang
went to Moon Washing Pond to check out the demon realm.
Senior Lu Li
was so busy patrolling the place
and trying to get hold of the herb
that he really had his hands full.
Can he really get that King Herb?
He already has a clue.
Now it's just a matter of when he gets it.
You may leave.
Senior Du,
what I promised
will be done.
It's just that if you cover it up like this,
it makes people suspicious.
Bai Feng.
Is it accurate that
there's an immortal herb that has grown fine for thousands of years
in the Pearl Pavilion?
I hope it doesn't backfire.
I don't want it to affect our future in the mansion.
Senior Du.
Today's Marquis Wuyang practiced martial arts at the age of three,
and achieved enlightenment at the age of ten.
He defended justice with a three-foot sword.
He was chosen to be the Lord
at the age of 16 by the former Marquis Wuyang.
In order to be strong,
he would
stop at nothing.
I thought
you would be a lot like the master,
resourceful and courageous.
Now,
why have you become so timid?
How can I not believe what you say?
It's just that this is very important,
and I want to be discreet.
Who would have thought that
such a secret could be hidden
in that deserted Pearl Pavilion?
It's a good thing you told me before.
Otherwise, if Lu Li offers the King Herb,
I'm afraid
there's no place for me in this mansion.
I'm glad you understand.
I will do the rest myself.
All you need to do is
distract brothers and sisters from the Pearl Pavilion.
If it works, you can take the credit.
If it fails,
I won't drag you down.
I do appreciate your efforts.
When I control Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
I'll repay you.
Well, I got to go.
I'd like to ask you to borrow some demon fire,
which can burn for seven days.
Okay.
I'll give it to you.
This demon fire only burns living things.
And it won't burn out.
Make good use of it.
Liu Shao!
Senior Bai Feng.
Usually,
you are responsible for cleaning the Pearl Pavilion.
Then you're gonna have to
take care of these demon-banishing lights.
Yes.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
I have to be more careful.
But...
Not many people go to the Pearl Pavilion normally.
Do we need so many lights?
Because no one usually goes there.
What if some demons
go in there?
Junior Liu Shao.
Am I right?
Yes, you're right.
I'll go.
Master!
We're not going to ask you for the herb anymore.
You need to stop avoiding me.
Come out!
All right.
I'll clean up
and leave you alone.
Girl, why don't you eat?
Is your nose not working
or these osmanthus cakes aren't sweet?
Because I want to eat with you.
Little girl,
since when do you have a conscience?
What happened?
This year's demon-banishing,
you even counted the Pearl Pavilion?
When I do the math,
no one has visited the Pearl Pavilion
for nearly a century.
Master, you mean
they didn't come to the Pearl Pavilion in the past?
No, no, no.
I scared them off when they got here.
I don't know what's going on this year,
with all these demon-banishing lights.
What's wrong?
Aren't you the one who laid them out?
Is there a problem?
Demon fire! Run! Run!
Xue.
Where is Liu Shao?
Senior Bai Feng asked her
to lay out the demon-banishing lights in the Pearl Pavilion.
She's still not back.
Bai Feng?
How long has she been gone?
Seems like a few hours ago.
Fire!
The Pearl Pavilion is on fire!
Get some water.
The Pearl Pavilion is on fire.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Put out the fire.
Why can't this fire go out?
This demon fire was enchanted.
Once it burns, water can't put it out. The fire will burn for seven days.
Girl, run!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry up!
Help! Help!
This way!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Get some water!
Hurry!
-Here, give it to me! -Get some more water.
No, we need to find a way out of here.
Or we'll be consumed by the demon fire.
It doesn't work.
Look at the aperture on the roof.
The demon fire
attached to the boundary of the Pearl Pavilion.
There's no way a living thing can escape.
What are we gonna do?
Girl!
I'll use my psychic powers
to help you fight your way out.
Otherwise, it'll be too late.
What about you?
Just leave me alone.
I can't get out.
Even if I can stop the fire,
I can't get out of here.
But you are different.
You still have a chance.
What are you doing?
Senior Xueyang gave you this hairpin
because
this is the key to unlock the boundary of the Pearl Pavilion.
You already knew that, didn't you?
Give it back to me!
If she were alive,
she wouldn't need you to do this.
But she's gone.
She's gone!
This hairpin is all I have.
You're gonna take it away, too?
Master!
This... is the last thing she left me.
I can't live without it.
Liu Shao!
Master.
You can keep it if you want.
But,
we can't lose.
This way!
Get some more water!
Lu Li.
Liu Shao!
Are you in there? Answer me!
Not enough. Go get some more water!
Okay! Coming!
Here.
Get another bucket!
Lu Li, don't go!
It's too dangerous!
I just checked.
There's nothing in there!
Lu Li!
Coming! Coming!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
[Pearl Pavilion]
Hurry up!
Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
Take me away.
Okay.
I'll take you out.
I can't believe their psychic power
radiates such power.
[Pearl Pavilion]
After all these years,
you finally got over it.
I dare not go out.
I'm afraid if I walk out of here,
I'll never feel you again.
How could you not feel me?
Aren't you the master of plants?
The world in front of you
is the one I used to guard.
Every inch of the land
has been filled with my efforts.
Do you feel it?
Yes, Xueyang.
I feel it.
But... I still miss you.
The King Herb?
The King Herb.
Me?
Master!
-Your hair! -Your hair!
You kept your promise
and helped me out of the Pearl Pavilion.
And I kept my promise
to give you the immortal herb.
But you...
I...
What are you talking about?
Although my hair is white,
I'm still
a handsome master.
Girl,
help me put this on.
Is it pretty?
Yes.
All good things must come to an end.
This time
I really should go.
You two
are gonna get really bored without me.
You guys really miss me.
If you don't want me to leave, just tell me.
But even if tell me, I won't stay.
Master,
where are you going?
Go back to my immortal palace.
It's kind of
back to
where I came from.
So will we
see each other again?
Girl,
you have Lu Li with you.
You won't be lonely.
As long as we are bonded,
we will meet again.
Bye.
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
What's going on here?
I was gone for a day or two.
Such a big thing happened.
The Pearl Pavilion has stood
for thousands of years in the mansion.
How could it catch fire?
Tell me!
I think there must be some disciples
accidentally knocked over the demon-banishing lights.
That's how it caught fire.
I heard it was a demon fire.
And it never goes out.
My Lord.
I can testify that
it was indeed a demon fire.
The fire can't be put out by water.
The other day in the fire,
I found a grass demon.
It should be made of King Herbs.
I heard that
Junior Liu Shao
has been hanging out at the Pearl Pavilion lately.
She's probably looking for the herb, too.
Where is that herb demon?
The grass demon
disappeared after the fire.
My guess is that
he was trapped in the Pearl Pavilion.
He wanted to escape,
so he started the fire.
Junior Bai's inference made perfect sense.
I
think so too.
Shameless.
I heard
that the grass demon and Liu Shao are very personal friends.
When he left,
he had handed over the King Herb to Junior Liu Shao.
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao did get the herb.
She's waiting for Your Majesty to come back and present it.
She got it?
Liu Shao is so amazing.
She's not the average person.
It really is the King Herb.
It seems that heaven is not gonna kill me and there's a way out.
Liu Shao.
This time,
you've done a great job.
What about the demon fire?
Now that you've got the herb,
you redeemed yourselves.
I will let go of the burning of the Pearl Pavilion.